Hey, Monro.
>> Can y'all hear me? Good. We're all good.
>> We can hear you. Great.
>> Let me sit up real quick.
How are y'all doing?
>> We're doing great. First off, we just
want to say congratulations. We're so
happy to have you here in the Carolinas.
>> Me, too. Me, too.
>> All right. We're going to kick things
off with Chris Jenkins.
>> Hey, Monroe. Congratulations, sir.
>> I appreciate you. Hey, so um what's
something about you the Carolina Panther
fans won't see on film, but your
teammates will notice right away. Kind
of introducing you to this fan base,
>> man. My energy. I think I bring the
energy every single day, regardless if
it's a practice, a walkth through, or a
game, man. I'll bring the energy every
single day. So, I'm going to get on that
team and, you know, I might be a rookie,
but I'm going to bring the energy every
single day just because I don't think I
can go out there and play offensive line
without it. So, definitely my energy.
>> All right. Can Can you give me a moment
from your college career that really
shows um who you are as a player or even
a teammate?
>> Man, even Tennessee, I remember I think
I might have given up a sack that game,
but I just kept going and I just kept at
it and I just um I just kept uh I said
keep chopping every single every it was
it was a tough game. It was a shootout
and I just said keep chopping, keep
chopping, keep chopping. And you know,
we ended up winning that game even
though it wasn't my best game. So, I
mean, I want to I want to at the end of
the day, like the team's my team's my
thing, you know, like I'm a team player.
I love the team. I want the team to win
more than anything. And I think that
playing offensive line, that's what you
get. You got you got to play for the
team. So, um that's what I got.
>> Thank you. And congrats.
>> Thank you.
>> We'll go with Cassidy Hill.
>> Hey, Monroe. Congratulations.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Uh this this means you get to stay in
the Carolinas. What kind of uh what is
that like just kind of knowing that you
get to stay home in a sense?
>> I mean it's it's actually in insane
because my older brother he went to
school of Charlotte so he went to school
at Queens and Charlotte so it's like
it's like a cycle almost. I'm going up
there too and I'll be there up there
with him. So it's like uh I was up there
with him I guess. But I mean it's kind
of incredible. I mean I could I didn't
imagine this and I'm you know I'm so
happy that this is the case now. It's
like I get to stay up three hours from
the home and I get to basically stay at
home and I didn't I didn't do that
through the college recruiting process.
So I guess I owe it to my Carolina fans.
>> Is your brother still in Charlotte?
>> No, he's at home now, but he played
basketball up there for a little bit. So
he's uh he's super ecstatic as well.
>> So you know your way around a little bit
or at least have a guide.
>> I mean I do have definitely have a
guide. He was there for the two two and
a half years or something like that. So
I definitely do have a guide. And then I
also wanted to learn about uh tell me
about your basketball background
especially as a blocker.
>> Yeah. No. Uh I definitely wish I would
have I mean I en enrolled early to
Georgia to go play football but that
senior year I was thinking I was like
damn. I mean only if I was there I would
have uh been to go win a state
championship in my basketball team
because they were missing it big on the
team. But basketball background I mean
if it wasn't for my older brother uh who
was playing at Queens Charlotte I
probably wouldn't be so into basketball.
We got to play with each other uh his
senior year, my freshman year of high
school, which is a really good
experience for me and him. And uh no, I
definitely translate some of my
basketball background into my football
background or my football play.
>> How so?
>> I just think that, you know, pass
protection, especially as an offensive
lineman, is a lot to do with playing
defense in basketball. So, uh, like at
least changing direction wise, you're
trying to stay in front of defender in
basketball translates to the same thing
in football except I get to use my hands
and you can't do that in basketball.
>> Thank you.
>> We'll go with Steve Reed followed by
Bash Tai Her.
>> Hey, Monroe. Congratulations and uh,
welcome to Charlotte. Um, hey uh, just
curious, did you play exclusively uh, on
the left side, left tackle at Georgia?
>> Um, not exclusively. I played left this
last year. Uh started the whole time,
but my freshman and sophomore year I was
a swing tackle. So I was playing a lot
of swing tackles, especially my
sophomore year. I was left and right,
middle of a game, middle of a series,
didn't really matter. So I have pretty
much a good amount of experience on both
sides.
>> You uh do you prefer either side? You
feel more comfortable on either side?
>> Um I mean, because I played left, I'd
probably say left right now, but I mean,
you put me at right and you give me two
weeks, I'm gonna be the same player
there.
>> Excellent. Thanks,
Hi,
>> Monroe Bash her with Carolina Blitz.
Welcome to Carolina. Uh,
>> let's go.
>> I have a Are you You're from Mount
Pleasant, but did you grow up a Panthers
fan? What's your familiarity with the
team? Um, I mean, I I didn't grow up
really allegiance to any NFL team, but I
came here and um I think 2016 we moved
to South Carolina, but uh I have know a
lot of Carolina fans that are kind of
around me just being in the area and the
fact that like I really claim Carolina
more than I claim where I used to be
from and in Oregon. So, it's like now
that I get to really claim Carolina for
real, it's it's awesome.
>> Tell me about the draft party. Like
where are you at? Are you in Mount
Pleasant and and your family and
friends? Just give me set the scene for
me.
>> Yeah, I'm at home. Uh just our home
estates essentially. And uh you know, I
always kind of dreamed being at home
with my family and my mom and my dad did
a great job setting up the whole party.
I mean, they made it look amazing down
there and we're outside and enjoying the
whole environment just living in
Charleston, especially this time of
year. So, they did a great job and you
know, I'm really excited to No, I'm so
excited to be a Panther, but especially
being so close to home. It's really only
like three hours.
>> Thanks.
>> We'll go with Joe Pson followed by Phil
Orin.
>> Monroe, when did you kind of get the
sense that the Panthers were were high
on you and did you go into tonight
thinking there was a good chance this
could happen or no?
>> You know, I had some feedback from my
agent telling me that like, you know, if
I was still there, they would take me.
But, you know, I mean, you got to take
everything with a grain of salt cuz, you
know, I didn't know how this night was
going to go and I tried to get every
expectation out of my mind. And when it
finally came down to it and I was
sitting there and I think Detroit was
still on the clock and I I got a call
and I was like, "Oh, let me pick this
up." And this is like, "Hey, this is the
Carolina Panthers." I was like, "No way.
There's just no way." And I was just
like, it was surreal. And it's still
surreal. And I don't even know if it's
sitting quite yet that I'm staying home
and I'm only a three-hour drive from
home and it's it's closer than I was in
Athens. So, it's just it's still not
really setting in yet, but I'm imagining
that in the next 24 hours, maybe even
the next week, it's going to really hit
me that like I'm here now. I'm blocking
for a former teammate of mine, and it's
like it's everything I've ever wanted.
>> So, a followup, too. Like, you know,
they they're starting left tackle from
the last few years is hurt. They signed
Rasheed Walker in free agency.
What's your thought? I mean, are you
coming in here thinking you're going to
have like a red shirt or are you coming
in to start?
>> I mean, I think I can't go in without
the mentality to not start. I'm going to
go in there and I'm going to want to
give it my Sorry, I don't know if I lost
you, but um I want to go in there and I
want to start, you know. Um but I'm
going to go in there and, you know, try
to get my teammates better, too, and
hope they can get me better as a rookie.
So, um I'm excited to learn, but I'm
also excited to compete.
Monroe, you mentioned your your energy
that that you bring. Where where does
that come from? Like where does that
sort of passion for the game? Where did
that come from? When did that start?
>> I mean, I've been tossed in the line of
scrimmage since the day I was damn was
born. So, uh, I pretty much have had the
mentality. It's like, you know, not
every little kid wants to play offensive
line from the jump, but if you don't
grow a love for it, you're not going to
make it. And so I think I grew a love
for uh you know dominating the man in
front of me and making it fun and
playing with my other offensive lineman.
So I think the energy just came from
experience and especially playing at
Georgia. I got to play with so many good
offensive linemen and good teammates
that it just made it fun to play the
position. So I brought energy every
single day because I don't think you can
make it playing the position without it.
>> Appreciate it.
>> We have time for a couple more. We'll go
with Dennis Cox followed by Alex
>> Monroe. First of all, congratulations.
How do you feel your skill set matches
up with the Carolina Panthers system
offensively?
>> Yeah. No, for sure. I mean, I think I'm
an athletic tackle and I think that, you
know, it's it's awesome that, you know,
Bryce can really get out. He can move
around the pocket and I think that, you
know, I'm going to do a great job
protecting him, but I also think that,
you know, him, you know, running around
is going to help me. So, I think I'm
going to fit in pretty well.
>> Awesome. Congratulations again.
>> Thank you.
>> Hey, Monroe. Uh you mentioned um you're
going to be blocking for a former
teammate of yours and and Trevor. Um has
have you talked to Trevor in like the
couple minutes since uh this this draft?
Have you gotten a text from him or
something like that? And have you heard
from him in general about what it's like
in Carolina?
>> You know, I haven't really heard from
him. And the crazy part, I mean, I've
had a lot of, you know, calls going on,
especially from, you know, guys from the
Panthers and everybody else. But I know
that um you know, I really enjoyed
blocking from him. He was a great guy.
And you know, I it's I might give him a
call here sooner or later just to check
in on him because I don't think I've
talked to him in a little bit since uh
he left Georgia. So, it would be really
uh cool to talk to him and especially
block for him again because I don't
think he if he would have came back
another year, who wouldn't have known?
>> Yeah. Well, uh just just quickly, what
kind of uh what kind of privilege would
it be to block for him um at the NFL
level? I mean, knowing him as who he was
at Georgia, I mean, it's a great he's a
great guy, you know, and, you know,
having knowing a guy as good as he is
and, you know, how special of a football
player he is, it just makes it even more
of like a, you know, I got to do my job
for him, you know, so I'm going to go
out there and give him my all for him.
I'm going to go out and give for Bryce.
I'm going to do it all for the Panthers.
You know, I'm a team player.
>> We'll end with Joe Pearson.
So, speaking of guys and their reaction,
Dan Morgan said he got a text from Bryce
after he picked you and Bryce said,
"Let's go." Uh, curious uh what you
think about that and what you know about
Bryce.
>> I mean, I'm I watched him whenever he
was playing in the playoffs. That's for
sure. I know. I'm not I don't know if
they won the net either. I can't
remember. But, um I mean, I'm excited to
play for anybody and I hoping and he was
the same size as my other quarterback.
So, you know, I'm going to play with
better pad level. You know, I'm just
excited. I'm just excited to block for
block for him. I'm just excited to block
for the team.
>> What quarterback you referring to?
>> Gunnar Stockton.
>> Nice.
>> All right, Monroe. That's all the
questions that we have for you tonight.
Thank you so much for taking the time.
Congratulations. We can't wait to meet
you.
>> Yes, sir. Yes, man. Keep pounding. Keep
pounding.
>> Let's go.